boot-station.com 2009-09-27

# Privacy Notice : Tiffany & Co., Tiffany Store Tiffany Jewelry Tiffany&co.Tiffany necklaces&pendants

## Privacy Policy

TIFFANY & CO.  
727 Fifth Avenue  
New York, NY 10022 

Dear Visitor: 

We want you to know how we handle the information you send us via the internet. Our Privacy Policy adapts to the internet's dynamic environment. We keep you informed by updating this Privacy Policy as our procedures change. Please review it occasionally to remain informed. This Policy was last updated on December 28, 2005. This is the way we handle information: 

### Automatic Collection

Our web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name (not the email address) and records the visitor's browser and platform type (e.g., Netscape browser on a Microsoft platform). 

### Cookies

We use cookies to:   

  * Record the visitor's session information (such as the visitor's shopping selections when ordering), 
  * Record user-specific information on the pages the visitor selects for viewing, 
  * Retain the country of our site that you last visited. 

### Email Addresses

When a visitor gives us their email address, or sends us email correspondence, we retain their email address. We do not share our email lists with third parties for marketing purposes. We use email addresses to communicate with you regarding your orders and other matters regarding transactions between us or your customer relationship with us. We may also use your email address to share information about Tiffany & Co. products and services that may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving such promotional messages from us at any time. If we do send you a promotional email, you will be given the opportunity to decline receiving similar emails in the future. If you wish to decline receiving such emails in the future, [click here](http://www.boot-station.com/index.php?main_page=login).

### Visitor-Keyed Information

We retain information provided by our visitor, such as registration information, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number). [Click here](http://www.boot-station.com/index.php?main_page=login) to access this information. 

Our visitor also has the ability to correct inaccuracies in contact information and unique identifiers. To do so, [click here](http://www.boot-station.com/index.php?main_page=login). 

On request with verification, we will give the visitor a reminder with unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password). 

### Mailing Addresses

If you request a catalogue to be mailed to your postal address, you will be placed on our mailing list and you will receive periodic mailings from us. If you purchase through our catalogue, you may also receive mailings from other carefully screened companies to whom we may make such mailing lists available. (These lists do not include Tiffany & Co. charge card account holders). If you prefer, you can have your name put on our do-not-share list by writing to us at our address above. Please include your name and address as it appears on your mailing label. 

### Telephone Numbers

Visitors who give us their telephone numbers online will receive telephone contact from our representatives regarding orders or requests they have placed online. You may be contacted by one of our representatives conducting research with regard to your satisfaction with our service. Your participation is voluntary and you may opt-out at any time by telephoning us at 1-800-843-3269.

### Ad Servers

Tiffany & Co. does not have arrangements with any ad server companies for this website. 

### Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer data exchanged with our website server. All other data transfer is conducted through a secure phone line. 

### Bridal Registry Customers

Tiffany & Co. Bridal Registry customers may elect to have their Tiffany & Co. Registry available on WeddingChannel.com, the premier wedding website. The information provided by customers is transmitted via secure phone line to WeddingChannel.com. The WeddingChannel.com Privacy Policy may treat that information differently than outlined above.

### Children's Online Privacy

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act took effect April 21, 2000, and pertains to websites directed toward children under 13 years of age. Tiffany.com does not collect information on any person under 13 years. We ask that children do not submit information to us without the consent of a parent or guardian.   

### Disclosure

If required by law, court order or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise advisable, we may disclose your information.
